{
    "id": "9e2fe4c7b7df4d89b6ac381dd5684011",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Each of these boys ………………….cricket well.",
            "description": "Each is followed by a singular verb.",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "plays"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6375ad6d5404da090759963ed13d0b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone of them …………………… present.",
            "description": "Every, everyone, everybody etc. are followed by a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcb24e6c03dc4d0fbe9b4952bdd9654d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of them ................................ there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "172a184a6e054a74a1305e0dac56a502"
        },
        {
            "question": "They all helped ……………………..",
            "description": "Each other is used to talk about two people or things. Use one another for more than two. ",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "381f4cdd0cbf43b4a190e47a44d7c42a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let …………………….. get going.",
            "description": "Let is a verb and a pronoun used as its object should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8281ef20505c4df28ec780f7a92d0ee4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not as tall as ………………… is.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the subject of a verb should be in its subject form. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a637d1813734dafa4a6ca9ce34d089b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Go now and ...........................",
            "description": "Enjoy also need an object. This is an imperative sentence and obviously it is addressed to the second person (you).",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "enjoy yourself",
                "enjoy oneself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e45f9a5a91c4fbc9bd163541b89d415"
        },
        {
            "question": "His claim is more legitimate than ……………………..",
            "description": "We need a possessive pronoun here.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1e99d53d452e44cfa7252e634152745f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. are responsible for your failure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Only you",
                "You alone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a4b85b17c794050bbec65574f04c4af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whoever does best ……………………. get the price.",
            "description": "Here the relative clause whoever does best is the subject of the verb will and hence you cannot add another subject here. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "he will",
                "he would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0c92e21149d44e6a35bbfbaad4713a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… to the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both didn't go",
                "Neither went"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec14e8db3463401e90cfb12e7f1287ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. are bothers.",
            "description": "Second and third person pronouns go before I. ",
            "answers": [
                "He and I",
                "I and he",
                "I and him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "53ce07065d2543b69c7c32a6f1865ef8"
        }
    ]
}